

BIBIANA AMUNDARAY

INTERNATIONAL MARKETING



PROFILE

International Marketing professional with over five years experience creating and executing business and marketing strategies. Experienced in working with multinational and cross-functional teams in English and Spanish, building strong relationship with key stakeholders, and managing personnel. Interested in constant learning, culture, traveling, and people.



EXPERIENCE

ACCOUNT MANAGER

NgageU / Dubai, UAE / Oct. 2015 - Actual

App Publisher

- Contribute in the creation of brand elements for Trekk7, a mobile platform for restaurants and coffee venues designed to increase satisfaction for dining experiences.
- Create content for the website and App Store.
- Design a marketing plan for Trekk7 introduction phase of the product.
- Develop relationships with potential clients.

MARKET ANALYST

PPS Group / Miami, U.S. / Nov. 2014 -June 2015

Procurement, projects and service consultants

- Audited business objectives and strategies used during Q4 (August October 2014).
- Analyzed the market to develop new business opportunities by optimizing processes and negotiation with providers.

ACCOUNT MANAGER

Matchcode / Caracas, Venezuela / Feb. 2010 - August 2013

Oversaw strategic and tactical planning for RIM (BlackBerry) projects at POS in Venezuela and LATAM. Successfully developed and executed projects focused on market growth, brand awareness, and customer satisfaction by customizing HQ's strategies into local market.

- Collaborated in recruiting, selection, trainings, and allocation of over 200 sales representatives in POS.
- Created strategies at POS in order to boost sales and customer satisfaction.
- Coordinate merchandising material and BTL activities, product launches and special activities in order to guarantee brand equity and projects objectives accomplishment.





BIBIANA AMUNDARAY

INTERNATIONAL MARKETING

SKILLS



PRESENTATIONS

PEOPLE MANAGEMENT

MARKETING & SALES STRATEGY

COMMUNICATION

SOCIAL MEDIA

- Exceeded all quarterly targets for Channel and Open Market devices for twelve consecutive quarters by guaranteeing the correlation between trade and consumer marketing activities. Surpassed sales objectives by over 200% and increased profits by 75% during the first year.
- Developed strategies with top BlackBerry's distributors for +1000 stores in the country. Contributed to significant sales growth (25% in three months) by broadening relationship with retailers and distribution networks and ensuring ample product supply.
- Coordinated consumer's loyalty promotional activity resulting in the sale of more than 1,000 devices in three days before the official release of BlackBerry10 at POS.

PROMOTIONS COORDINATOR

EVENPRO / Caracas, Venezuela / May 2008 - Sep 2009

Leading marketing, promotions and mass entertainment company in Latin America.

To coordinate, lead and evaluate promotional activities. Inventory, market research, data analysis, markets indicators, reporting and personnel management.

- Executed nationwide sampling campaign for Mini Club Social (KRAFT) launching resulting in over a million people reached in a month and 15% sales growth within three months.
- Coordinated a contest for Palmolive in association with local designers obtaining 10% sales growth in one month.
- Supported in recruiting, selecting, orienting, and training promoters.



EDUCATION

MASTERS DEGREE IN INTERNATIONAL MARKETING

HULT International Business School / San Francisco, California / Sept 2013 - August 2014

- Board member in Business in Fashion Club and Digital Marketing Club (participated as a community manager during the SF Tech Week).
- Module abroad at Dubai campus, completing electives in: Luxury Marketing and Service Operations Management.
- Action Project: Business plan (business growth and service expansion) for an international airline, 1st place honored with excellence.

BACHELORS DEGREE IN CORPORATE COMMUNICATION

UNIVERSIDAD SANTA MARIA / Caracas, Venezuela / March 2003 - Feb. 2008

- Internship: Six months as a communication intern at Grupo Zoom (logistic company)

CERTIFICATIONS

- (2011- 2012) Certificate in Marketing Management / CIAP / Venezuela
- (2009) Certificate in Brand Management / IESA / Venezuela
- (2008-2009) Certificate in TV and Radio broadcasting, announcements and oratory, Universidad Central de Venezuela / Venezuela.



+971 55 1308137 | () BIBIAE12@GMAIL.COM